<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TravelApp</string>
    <string name="introTitle">Adventure Awaits – <font color='#3f95ec'>\n Travel World</font> with Us</string>
    <string name="subIntro">Your all-in-one travel guide for exploring destinations.</string>

    <string name="description_kennedy">Explore the fascinating world of space exploration at the Kennedy Space Center in Orlando, Florida. Experience interactive exhibits, meet astronauts, and learn about NASA s exciting history. Witness the space shuttles and rockets that made history. A must-visit destination for space enthusiasts and families alike.</string>
    <string name="description_french_quarter">Dive into the rich culture of New Orleans’ French Quarter, a blend of history, music, and modern charm. Explore vibrant streets filled with unique shops, restaurants, and art galleries. Experience the lively jazz music and culinary delights that make this neighborhood famous. A celebration of New Orleans Creole heritage and diverse culture.</string>
    <string name="description_old_faithful">Discover the power and beauty of Old Faithful in Yellowstone Park, Wyoming. Watch as the world-famous geyser erupts, a spectacular display of geothermal activity. Surrounding the geyser are stunning landscapes, including hot springs, wildlife, and hiking trails. A natural wonder that leaves visitors in awe of Earth’s raw power.</string>
    <string name="description_mammoth_cave">Journey through the world’s longest cave system at Mammoth Cave National Park in Kentucky. Explore winding tunnels and breathtaking chambers on guided tours. Learn about the cave’s rich geological history and its importance in American natural heritage. A thrilling experience for adventurers and nature lovers alike.</string>
    <string name="Gateway_Arch">The Gateway Arch in St. Louis, Missouri, symbolizes the westward expansion of the United States. Stand beneath this towering 630-foot monument and take in panoramic views of the city. Visit the museum beneath the Arch to learn about America’s journey west. An iconic American landmark that blends history with modern architecture.</string>
    <string name="Park_City">Park City, Utah, is an outdoor paradise for every season, from world-class skiing in the winter to scenic trails and hiking in the summer. Experience the charm of a historic mining town, now home to luxury resorts and lively festivals. Whether it’s adventure or relaxation, Park City offers something for everyone.</string>
    <string name="jackson_Hole">Nestled in Wyoming, Jackson Hole is a gateway to the stunning Grand Teton and Yellowstone National Parks. Known for its rugged terrain and breathtaking views, its a haven for outdoor lovers. Whether you’re skiing, hiking, or wildlife watching, Jackson Hole offers endless adventure. The town itself has a charming Western feel with art galleries and boutique shops.</string>
    <string name="Honolulu">Immerse yourself in the vibrant Hawaiian culture and tropical beauty of Honolulu. Enjoy the stunning beaches, clear waters, and a variety of water sports, from surfing to snorkeling. Experience the islands rich heritage through historical sites, delicious local food, and lively cultural festivals. Honolulu combines adventure, relaxation, and breathtaking natural landscapes.</string>
    <!-- Add descriptions for your objects here -->
</resources>